

52, 11th Main Road

Banashankari Stage II

Bengaluru, INDIA 560070

▼ WHC9+8C BSK

Pvthon 3

☆ varungupta3009@gmail.com

**&** +91 97398 56528

್ಲಿ varungupta3009

# Experience



## Global IT: Data and Reporting Analyst

Hewlett Packard Enterprise Feb 2021 – Present (3 mos)



#### **Penetration Tester**

Center for Information Security, Forensics and Cyber Resilience May 2020 – Sep 2020 (5 mos)



### Student Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University
Jan 2019 – Sep 2020 (1 yr 9 mos)



### Software Engineer

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

## Education



#### **PES University**

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 – 2021



#### R. V. PU College

Pre-University, Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi, Computer Science 2015 – 2017



## Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka

### **Publications & Awards**

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier

IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

# Languages

English Hindi Kannada

## Hobbies

 X Virtual Aviation

ء	N/	اررد	iح
	IVI	ıus	IC.

# Knowledge and Skills

Experience			
Skill			
JavaScript			
Experience			
Skill	_		
C/C++			
Experience			
Skill			
Windows 7/8/10			
Experience	_		
Skill	-		
Eventend Design and Development			
Frontend Design and Development  Experience			
Skill			
Full-Stack Web Development			
Experience			
Skill			
Angular (TS), React (JS/TS)			
Experience			
Skill			
WordPress, CMS			
Experience			
Skill	_		
Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator			
Experience	-		
Skill	-		
Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro			
Experience	-		
Skill			
Blender, Pixar Renderman			
Experience			
Skill			
Cloud Architechture (GCP)			
Experience			
Skill			

Generated at https:resume.VRG.rock

## About me

I am a programmer and experienced web-developer, fluent in Python, C++, C#, Go with over 9 years of experience in Python and C++, and moderately versed in 7 other languages. I am a polymath and love to explore and try new technologies and fiddling with anything related to computers or the Windows OS in general. I am also a graphics designer and a hobbyist hacker.

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile for real-time accurate information, to stay regularly updated, and to get in touch with me instantly.

